salecalc.com 2019-09-12

# Privacy Policy | Salecalc.com Blog

This privacy policy sets out how Salecalc.com (“we” or “us” or “our”) uses and protects any information that you give when you use our websites, mobile applications, tablet applications, and/or desktop applications (collectively, “Services”, or, each individually, a “Service”).  Salecalc.com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected.  Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using our Services, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.  Salecalc.com may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.  You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.  This policy is effective from 30th of July, 2012.

## What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * contact information including email address
  * demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
  * other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

## What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with better Services, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * For you to send us feedback via various channels such as through email, our blog, or our forums.
  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.  We may contact you by email.  We may use the information to customize our Services according to your interests.

## How we use cookies

A cookie contains information that can be transferred to your computer or other electronic device.  The cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site.  Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual.   The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.  We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages on our websites are being used.  This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our websites in order to tailor it to customer needs.  We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes.  Overall, cookies help us provide you with better Services, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not.  A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.  You can choose to accept or decline cookies.  Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer.  This may prevent you from taking full advantage of our Services.

## Links to websites

Our Services may contain links to websites that we do not own or operate.  Once you have used these links to leave our Services, you should note that we do not have any control over such websites.  Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement.  You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
